("Truly Madly Deeply")
(soft pop music)
♪ I'll be your dream, I'll be your wish ♪
♪ I'll be your fantasy ♪
♪ I'll be your hope, I'll be your love ♪
♪ Be everything that you need ♪
♪ I love you more with every breath ♪
♪ Truly, madly, deeply do ♪
♪ I will be strong, I will be faithful ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm counting on ♪
♪ A new beginnin' ♪
♪ A reason for livin' ♪
♪ A deeper meaning, yeah ♪
♪ I wanna stand with you on a mountain ♪
♪ I wanna bathe with you in the sea ♪
♪ I wanna lay like this forever ♪
♪ Until the sky falls down on me ♪
♪ And when the stars are shining
brightly in the velvet sky ♪
♪ I'll make a wish, send it to heaven ♪
♪ And make you want to cry ♪
♪ The tears of joy for all the
pleasure and the certainty ♪
♪ That we're surrounded by
the comfort and protection ♪
♪ Of the highest powers ♪
♪ In lonely hours ♪
♪ The tears devour you ♪
♪ And I wanna stand
with you on a mountain ♪
♪ I wanna bathe with you in the sea ♪
♪ I wanna lay like this forever ♪
♪ Until the sky falls down on me ♪
♪ Oh, can you see it, baby ♪
♪ You don't have to close your eyes ♪
♪ It's standin' right before you ♪
♪ All that you need will surely come ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
♪ I'll be your dream, I'll be your wish ♪
♪ I'll be your fantasy ♪
♪ I'll be your hope, I'll be your love ♪
♪ Be everything that you need ♪
♪ I'll love you more with every breath ♪
♪ Truly, madly, deeply do ♪
♪ I wanna stand with you on a mountain ♪
♪ I wanna bathe with you in the sea ♪
♪ I wanna lay like this forever ♪
♪ Until the sky falls down on me ♪
♪ I wanna stand with you on a mountain ♪
♪ I wanna bathe with you in the sea ♪
♪ Well, I want to live like this forever ♪
♪ Until the sky falls down on me ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh yeah ♪
♪ Uh, uh ♪
♪ La, la, da, da, da, da ♪
♪ La, la, da, da, da, da, da ♪